All from the simple setup that I actually described. So my wife has been field testing some of our microscopes by washing my clothes whenever I forget them in the dryer. So it turns out they're waterproof, and -- (Laughter) — right here is just fluorescent water, and I don't know if you can actually see this. This also shows you how the projection scope works. You get to see the beam the way it's projected and bent. Can we get the lights back on again? So I'm quickly going to show you, since I'm running out of time, in terms of how much it costs for us to manufacture, the biggest idea was roll-to-roll manufacturing, so we built this out of 50 cents of parts and costs. (Applause) And what this allows us to do is to think about a new paradigm in microscopy, which we call use-and-throw microscopy. I'm going to give you a quick snapshot of some of the parts that go in. Here is a sheet of paper. This is when we were thinking about the idea. This is an A4 sheet of paper. These are the three stages that you actually see. And the optical components, if you look at the inset up on the right, we had to figure out a way to manufacture lenses in paper itself at really high throughputs, so it uses a process of self-assembly and surface tension to build achromatic lenses in the paper itself. So that's where the lenses go. There are some light sources. And essentially, in the end, all the parts line up because of origami, because of the fact that origami allows us micron-scale precision of optical alignment. So even though this looks like a simple toy, the aspects of engineering that go in something like this are fairly sophisticated. So here is another obvious thing that we would do, typically, if I was going to show that these microscopes are robust, is go to the third floor and drop it from the floor itself. There it is, and it survives. So for us, the next step actually is really finishing our field trials. We are starting at the end of the summer. We are at a stage where we'll be making thousands of microscopes. That would be the first time where we would be doing field trials with the highest density of microscopes ever at a given place. We've started collecting data for malaria, Chagas disease and giardia from patients themselves. And I want to leave you with this picture. I had not anticipated this before, but a really interesting link between hands-on science education and global health. What are the tools that we're actually providing the kids who are going to fight this monster soup for tomorrow? I would love for them to be able to just print out a Foldscope and carry them around in their pockets. Thank you. (Applause)
Tout ça grâce au simple équipement que je vous ai décrit. Ma femme a réalisé des essais sur le terrain pour certains microscopes. Elle lave mes vêtements quand je les oublie dans le sèche-linge. Il s'avère que les microscopes sont imperméables aussi. (Rires) - Quand je le plonge dans de l'eau fluorescente, vous pouvez voir comment fonctionne le principe de projection. Vous pouvez voir le rayon tel qu'il est projeté et diffracté. Peut-on rallumer les lumières ? Puisqu'il me reste peu de temps, je vais vous parler rapidement du coût de fabrication. L'idée centrale est de fabriquer à partir de rouleaux. Nos coûts de production sont de 50 cents. (Applaudissements) C'est un nouveau paradigme : la microscopie jetable. Je vais vous montrer rapidement quelques composants. Voilà une feuille de papier, format A4. Voilà les trois étapes, très visibles. Vous voyez les composants optiques en haut à droite. On a dû développer dans le papier un système de production de lentilles à haut rendement. On utilise un processus d'auto-assemblage et de tension de surface pour fabriquer des lentilles achromatiques en papier. Donc, les lentilles vont là. Il y a des sources de lumière. Fondamentalement, tous les composants s'alignent à cause de l'origami. L'origami permet en effet une incroyable précision d'alignement des éléments optiques. Alors même si ça ressemble à un simple jouet, l'ingénierie que nous appliquons est vraiment sophistiquée. Je pourrais aussi vous démontrer que ces microscopes sont robustes en le jetant du troisième étage. Le voici, et il fonctionne toujours. Les essais de terrain sont notre prochaine étape Nous commencerons à la fin de l'été. Nous allons fabriquer des milliers de microscopes. Ce sera une grande première de réaliser des tests sur le terrain avec un nombre record de microscopes concentrés sur un endroit donné. Nous avons commencé à recueillir chez des patients des données sur le paludisme, la maladie de Chagas et le Giarda. Je vais terminer avec cette image. C'était tout à fait imprévu mais nous avons découvert un lien intéressant entre l'enseignement pratique des sciences et la santé mondiale. Quels sont les outils que nous allons transmettre à nos enfants afin qu'ils puissent combattre ce bouillon de monstres? J'aimerais beaucoup qu'ils puissent imprimer un "Foldscope" pour l'emporter dans leur poche. Merci. (Applaudissements)